-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影子
翻译: 脸圆圆 一横 初见
校对: 影子
一千年前...
织布人部落建立了一个暗杀组织
他们为了重建世界的秩序 在混乱边缘执行任务
他们自称为"兄弟会"
六周前...
# 祝你生日快乐 亲爱的珍妮丝 #
# Happy birthday, dear Janice. #
# 祝你生日快乐! #
# Happy birthday to you! #
今天是我那个厌食症老板的生日
It's my anorexic boss' birthday.
这就意味着在办公室的时候要承受无比巨大的压力...
This means there's a certain amount of inter-office pressure...
来站在这个会议桌旁...
to stand around the conference table...
吃着恶心的食物 还得装出一副尊敬她的样子
eating crappy food and pretending to worship her.
这个真好吃
That's so good.
假装五分钟 珍妮丝并没有让我们的生活很糟糕
Acting for five minutes like Janice doesn't make all our lives miserable,
那只不过是我一天中最艰难的工作罢了
is the hardest work I'll do all day.
我工作的职位名称叫客户经理
My job title is account manager.
其实以前我被叫做客户服务代表
I used to be called an account service representative,
但是一个咨询顾问说 我们应该管理我们的顾客...
but a consultant told us we needed to manage our clients...
而不是服务他们
and not service them.
我有一个既不能管理也不能服务的女友
I have a girlfriend whom I neither manage nor service.
这是我最好的朋友拜瑞 正在宜家餐桌上干她
That's my best friend, Barry, fucking her on an IKEA kitchen table.
我可是花了好价钱买了那张餐桌
I picked up for a really good price.
我最近觉得很难去在乎什么事情
I'm finding it hard to care about anything these days.
事实上 我唯一在乎的事就是我不在乎任何事这一现状
In fact, the only thing I do care about is the fact that I can't care about anything.
说真的 这让我很困扰
Seriously. It worries me.
我的名字叫韦斯利・吉布森
My name is Wesley Gibson.
在我七天大的时候 我父亲就离开了我
My dad walked out on my mom when I was seven days old.
有时候我在想他到底有没有过望着我蓝色的眼睛问问自己
Sometimes I wonder if he ever looked into my baby blues eyes and asked himself,
"我是刚刚做了21世纪最无关紧要的人的父亲吗?"
"Did I just father the most insignificant asshole of the 21st century?"
如果你能在二十八号之前把我的委托物给我的话... 是的
Well, if you could get me the consignment to me by the 28th... Yeah.
你面前有号码吗?
Do you have the numbers in front of you?
放松
Relax.
如果你的名字出现了的话 你已经死了
If your name had come up, you'd be dead already.
最近出现了一些意想不到的失误
We've had some unexpected losses recently.
我们想知道...
We'd like to know...
我们的敌人是从哪里得到军火的
where our competitor is getting his munition.
这个子弹很干净
It's clean.
什么意思?
Meaning?
意思就是难以追踪
Meaning it's untraceable.
你的对手非常聪明
Your competitor's very smart.
趴下!
Get down!
该死
Fuck it.
没人能离开兄弟会 克洛斯
No one leaves the Fraternity, Cross.
我对兄弟会有了新的看法
I have a new perspective on the Fraternity.
小心点儿
Careful.
你没办法毁掉已经存在上千年的东西的
You don't destroy something that's been around for a thousand years.
兄弟会已经毁了 他坏了规矩
It's already destroyed. He broke the code.
我要阻止这一切
I have to stop this.
- 真的吗?  - 你自己知道的
- Really?  - You know this.
那你为什么不来当面见我?
So why don't you face me yourself?
你这是送羊入虎口
Never send sheep to kill a wolf.
他们只不过是诱饵
They were just the decoys.
再见 X先生
Goodbye, Mr X.
你这是送羊入虎口
Never send sheep to kill a wolf.
他们只不过是诱饵
They were just the decoys.
韦斯利!
Wesley!
怎么了?
What is it?
什么叫"怎么了"? 你听听
What do you mean, "What is it"? Listen.
这么吵 我怎么睡得好?
Well, how am I suppose to sleep with all that fucking racket?
你到底打算什么时候才搬家 好让我们不用每天早上被这玩意儿吵醒?
When are we gonna move so we don't have to wake up to that shit?
我还挺喜欢的
I kind of like it.
这该死的声音能够盖过你心中焦虑的声音
It helps to drown out the sound of your annoying, fucking voice.
拜托了 再让我睡会儿
Now, please, let me sleep.
你到底有没有考虑过我们的谈话?
Have you even thought about our talk?
考虑过
Yes.
哪一次?
Which one?
很好 真的太好了
Perfect. That's perfect.
记得喂安娜贝尔
Feed Annabelle.
抱歉
Sorry.
哦 我了个去
Oh, my fucking God.
我希望你桌子上的那个不是我的财务报表
I hope that's not my billing report sitting on your desk.
真不巧啊 还真是
Holy shit on an altar, it is.
我希望一个小时后这份报表能出现在我的桌上
I want that report on my desk in one hour.
好吧 各位 我们还要再加班一个小时...
Okay, everybody, we're all gonna stay an extra hour...
想要听点儿坏消息吗?
Want to hear something sad?
我还得买个人体工学键盘来控制我的重复压力性损伤
I need an ergonomic keyboard to keep my repetitive stress injury in check.
就是因为这些我来回念叨的小事而倍感压力真的是太悲哀了
Just the fact that I repeat something enough that it causes me stress is fucking sad.
干得好 兄弟 你看到拜瑞了吗?
Nice job, dude. You seen Barry?
他"又"去看牙医了
He had to go to the dentist. Again.
太棒了!
Yes!
拜瑞!
Barry!
你说他们这儿有紧急避孕药吗?
You think they have that morning-after pill here?
那个很有用的 碾碎了 然后放到她的煎蛋卷里
That thing works. Crush it up, put it in her omelette,
"嘿 宝贝 在床上吃早餐哦" 简直安全的不得了
"Hey, baby, breakfast in bed." You can never be too safe.
天啊
Oh, God.
我把钱包弄丢了
I lost my wallet somewhere.
一起算吗?
All this together?
- 不用 不用了  - 一起
- No, no.  - Yes.
他真够哥们儿
He is the man.
- 总共多少?  - 哦 加上这个
- How much is it?  - Oh. Plus this.
二十块四毛二
$20.42.
西瓜味儿
Watermelon.
小弟弟最爱
Chicks dig it.
谢谢
Thanks.
下次见
See you next time.
晚安
Have a good night.
我超爱这种能量饮料 兄弟
I love these energy drinks, man.
感觉能量饮料能让我净化
I'm almost, like, kind of on an energy drink cleanse,
我早餐喝一瓶 午餐喝两瓶或者三瓶
where I do one for breakfast and then, like, two or three for lunch.
我够哥们儿?
I'm the man?
是啊 没错 拜瑞 我够哥们儿
Yeah, right, Barry, I'm the man.
说真的 我实在是太够哥们儿了
In fact, I'm so much the man,
我有一张长期药物处方 以此来控制我的焦虑症
I have a standing prescription for medication to control my anxiety attacks.
天啊 我希望有别的什么能缓解我的压力
God, I wish I had something else to relieve my stress.
你好 韦斯利
Hello, Wesley.
总有那么些人 很漂亮的人
You know, there are people, beautiful people,
你希望她们以不同的眼光 不同的立场来看你
you just wish they could see you in a different setting, a different place,
而不是看你在哪儿 你会成为什么人
instead of where you are, what you've become.
妮可真够正点
Nicole is so hot.
什么?
What?
炸弹就要爆炸了
Boom goes the dynamite.
但更多时候 你都在希望自己别这么磨叽...
But most of all, you wish you weren't such a pussy...
老是想一些不可能改变的事情
for wishing for things that will never change.
我全能的神啊 你就跟发春一样站在那儿
Good God Almighty, you're over here like it's spring fucking break,
而我还没拿到我的财务报表
and I still don't have that billing report.
我为什么还让你呆在这儿 韦斯利?
Why do I even keep you around, Wesley?
我马上做好 珍妮丝
I'll get it done, Janice.
说得好像你以前没跟我说过这话似的 "我马上做好"
Like I never heard that before. "I'll get it done."
"我马上做好 我马上做好 珍妮丝"
"I'll get it done. I'll get it done, Janice."
"我马上做好"
"I'll get it done."
怎么不帮你自己说几句话?
Why don't you have anything to say for yourself?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你真的一无是处
Well, you're worthless.
我才是很抱歉的那一个 抱歉雇佣了你这么个废物
I'm the one who's sorry I hired your ass.
你知道一天结束时最好的事是什么吗?
You know what the best thing is about the end of the day?
那就是明天一切重新来过
Tomorrow it starts all over again.
余额不足 你是个废物 对/不对
你破产了 最好的朋友上了你女朋友 你知道 却窝囊得什么都干不了 对/不对
- 嗨 你好吗?  - 很好
- Hi. How you doing?  - Good.
- 不好意思?  - 你说抱歉说太多了
- I'm sorry?  - You apologise too much.
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
我认识你父亲
I knew your father.
我父亲在我出生后一周就走了 所以...
My father left the week I was born, so...
你父亲昨天死在在中央大楼的屋顶上
Your father died yesterday on the rooftop of the Metropolitan Building.
抱歉
Sorry.
听着 这边有很多酒精饮料 所以...
Look, the liquor rounds are just over there, so...
你父亲曾经是世界顶尖的暗杀者之一
Your father was one of the greatest assassins who ever lived.
杀了他的那个男的就在你后面
The man who killed him is behind you.
这人刚刚开枪了...
This guy's just shooting up...
对不起 对不起
Sorry. Sorry.
什么... 哦 我的天! 我的天啊! 刚刚到底发生了什么?
What... Oh, my God! Oh, my God! What the fuck just happened?
拜托了! 拜托了! 拜托再开快点儿
Please! Please! Please drive faster.
- 拜托你安静点儿  - 再开... 再开快点儿
- Please be quiet.  - Please drive... Please drive faster.
拜托... 拜托你要理解我是很惜命的!
Please... Please understand that I care about my life!
我不知道你到底是怎么惹了那个家伙
I don't know what the fuck you did to piss this guy off,
但是你得让我下车 然后去报警!
but you're gonna have to let me out and call the cops!
嘿! 嘿!
Hey! Hey!
你要干嘛? 哦 该死! 你疯了吗?
What are you doing? Oh, shit! Are you crazy?
哦 该死
Oh, shit!
我想我们甩掉他了 我们甩掉他了
I think we lost him. I think we lost him.
能不能在下个拐角处放我下去?
Could you let me out at the next corner, please?
该死!
Shit!
靠!
Fuck!
哦 该死!
Oh, shit!
他就在那儿!
He's right there!
听着 我是个会计 我就是一会计
Look, I'm an accountant. I'm just an accountant.
我靠!
Oh, fuck!
他可真他妈的执着
He's fucking persistent, you know.
靠!
Fuck!
快点好好教训他!
You kick his ass!
打他啊!
Shoot him!
你在干嘛? 你干嘛打咱们车的玻璃 哈?
What are you doing? What are you shooting our car for, huh?
- 你疯了吗?  - 抓着方向盘
- Are you crazy?  - Grab the wheel.
你要去哪儿?
Where are you going?
快回来!
Get back in here!
天啊!
Oh, my God!
该死! 对不起
Oh, damn! I'm sorry.
- 枪!  - 什么?
- Gun!  - What?
在座位下面?
Under the seat!
给
Here.
哦 我靠!
Oh, shit!
我靠!
Shit!
- 小心!  - 让开!
- Look out!  - Get out!
小心! 哦 我的天!
Look out! Oh, my God!
我靠!
Shit!
对不起!
I'm sorry!
小心后面!
Behind you!
操
Fuck.
该死 该死
Shit. Shit.
你好
Hello.
我没钱也...
I don't have any money or...
我本以为...
I thought he'd be...
他会更高
taller.
更高?
Taller?
先生...
Sir...
先生 我昨天就试着向这位女士解释我是个会计了
Sir, I've been trying to explain to the lady here that I'm an accountant.
我是个客户服务代表... 是个客户经理
I'm an account service representative... I'm an account manager.
我相信如果你打给我的老板珍妮丝的话
And I'm sure that if you call my boss, Janice,
无论什么误会 她都能解释清楚的
she'd fill you in on whatever has gone wrong.
你可以给她发邮件或者... 她会解释清楚的
You can contact her by email or... She'll put you straight.
打掉苍蝇的翅膀
Shoot the wings off the flies.
我不知道你什么意思
I don't know what that means.
打掉苍蝇的翅膀
Shoot the wings off the flies.
我真的觉得你把我和别人搞混了
I really think you have me mixed up with somebody else.
我数三下
On three.
你开枪 或者我开枪
Either you shoot, or I do.
一
One.
好吧
Okay.
二
Two.
我看都看不见他们!
I can't even see them!
三
Three.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
那根本不可能
That's impossible.
在今天之前 很多事情对于你来说都是不可能吧
A lot of things for you weren't possible before today.
你所感受到的 并不是什么恐慌症
What you experienced, Wesley, was not a panic attack.
你的心跳达到每分钟四百以上
Your heart was beating in excess of 400 beats per minute,
如此高的心率可以将大量的肾上腺素输送进你的血液
sending abundant amounts of adrenaline into your bloodstream.
这也让你能够比平常人有更快的反应能力
This allows you to see and react faster than normal.
这世界上仅有一少部分人能做到
Only a few people in the world can do that.
你父亲可以 你也可以
Your father could do it and you can do it.
只要一点训练 你就能学会控制这种力量
With a little work, you can learn to control these attacks.
离我远一点
Stay away from me.
后退
Just stay back from me.
我拿着枪呢 先生 对吧?
I have a gun, sir. All right?
我叫斯隆
My name is Sloan.
这位是福克斯
This is Fox.
这周围的所有人都精于刺杀
And the others you see around you are all very good at killing.
所以 如果我是你 我会用枪指着我
So, if I were you, I'd keep the gun pointed at me.
你不会想瞄准他们中的任何一个的
You don't wanna point it at any of them.
这样好多了
That's better.
- 你疯了  - 没有
- You're insane.  - No.
你的血管里流淌着杀手的血液...
Insanity is wasting your life as a nothing...
浪费生命对你来说才是真正的疯狂
when you have the blood of a killer flowing in your veins.
你就像是笼中猛兽 只需要一把释放你的钥匙
Insanity is being shit on, beat down,
但你不重视你的能力 不利用你的能力...
coasting through life in a miserable existence...
最终只能悲惨的过完人生 你才是疯了
when you have a caged lion locked inside and a key to release it.
你拿着的这把枪是今西17号 它曾经属于你父亲
This gun you're holding is an Imanishi 17. It belonged to your father.
他甚至能用这把枪指挥交响乐团
He could conduct a symphony orchestra with it.
而你 将会拿着这把枪杀掉那个冷血杀死你父亲的人
And you're going to use it to kill the man who shot him down in cold blood.
- 我不能...  - 和昨晚想杀你的是同一个人
- I can't...  - The same man who tried to kill you tonight.
你父亲是我们的一员
Your father was one of us.
我们是暗杀组织 是命运的武器
A fraternity of assassins. The weapons of fate.
我们已经将他所有的财产转移给你了
We've transferred all of his assets over to you.
我向你保证 财产相当丰厚
And let me assure you, they are substantial.
这是你等待已久的命运...
It is your long-awaited destiny...
加入我们吧
to join us.
后退 后退
Back off. Back off.
你根本不了解我
You don't know anything about me.
离我远点儿 离我远点儿
Stay away from me. Stay away from me.
你不离我远点儿吗?
You stay away from me?
能不能离我远点儿? 能不能让我过去?
You stay away from me, please? Will you let me through?
你有没有过那种做梦做到一半然后突然醒来
You know when you have a dream and you're half awake,
而那个梦还在你脑中盘旋的感觉吗?
but it's still in the fringe of your brain?
然后你睁开眼睛 庆幸刚刚那是梦
Then you open your eyes and you're so damn glad it was a dream.
根本不是这么回事儿
This was nothing like that.
对不起 能不能先让我用下? 谢谢
I'm sorry. Could you just give me one second? Thank you.
该死
Oh, shit.
韦斯利
Wesley.
你怎么了?
What's up with you?
你什么意思啊?
What do you mean?
你... 你今天来得很早
You're... You're here early.
你... 你看起来很有精神
Is... You seem a little pepped up.
- 你还好吗?  - 当然 我很好
- You all right?  - Well, yeah.
很好
Yeah.
我觉得我自己...
I guess I feel...
有那么点儿不一样了
kind of different.
好吧 我打算去拿点儿便利贴 你要吗?
Whatever. I'm gonna go get some Post-it Notes. Do you want one?
- 不要  - 真不要?
- No.  - Really?
- 真的  - 好吧
- Yeah.  - Okay.
我的苍天啊 我还没拿到我的财务报表
Jesus H. fucking Popsicle, I still don't have my billing reports,
但你还有空坐在这儿查你那些狗屁玩意儿
but you've got time to sit here and Google your ass off.
好吧 我只知道一件事
Well, I know one thing.
下个礼拜你就会拿到你的评估
You've got your review coming up next week,
我已经迫不及待想勾全了那些选项
and I can't wait to start checking me off some big fucking boxes.
态度 差评! 表现 差评!
Attitude, poor! Performance, poor!
业务能力 差评!
Management skills, poor!
合作能力强 简直就是个笑话
Works well with others. That's a fucking joke.
这是什么破玩意儿? 这混蛋是谁?
What is this bullshit? Who's this prick?
某些衰人在中央大楼上被爆头...
Some loser gets his head blown off at the Metropolitan...
给我闭嘴!
Shut the fuck up!
她也就有那么一点微不足道的力量
She has one single iota of tenuous power.
就想让每个人都听她的
She thinks she can push everyone around.
你不需要这玩意儿
You don't need this.
我理解你
I understand.
你的初中生活一定很辛苦
Junior high must have been kind of tough,
但并不代表你有权利把你的员工当畜生 珍妮丝
but it doesn't give you the right to treat your workers like horseshit, Janice.
我知道大家都在嘲笑你 珍妮丝
I know we laugh at you, Janice.
我们都知道你把果冻面包圈放在最上面的抽屉里
We all know you keep your stash of jelly doughnuts in the top drawer of your desk.
但是我想让你知道...
But I want you to know...
如果你没这么贱的话 我们都会觉得很抱歉
if you weren't such a bitch, we'd feel sorry for you.
我会为你感到抱歉
I do feel sorry for you.
但是现在的情况是 你的表现
But as it stands, the way you behave,
我觉得我可以代表整个办公室的人...
I feel I can speak for the entire office...
对你说...
when I tell you...
去你妈的
go fuck yourself.
真棒 兄弟 谁是真汉子?
Yeah. That was great, bro. Who's the man?
操你妈
我是
I'm the man.
摄像头拍下嫌犯面容
通缉令
这是个坏主意
That's a bad idea.
找不到你的钥匙了吗?
Couldn't find your keys, huh?
这会经常用到 你会教我的对吗?
That could be handy. You going to teach me that?
我会需要的
I might need that.
你叫"福克斯" 对吧? 这是什么? 是代号吗?
So, Fox, right? What is that? Is that a call sign?
就像"壮志凌云"(汤姆・克鲁斯主演电影)里的小牛?
Is it like Maverick in Top Gun?
你要是告诉我 就得杀了我?
You could tell me, but you'd have to kill me?
开玩笑的
I'm just kidding.
十七号纺织厂
彼得!
Peter!
检查一下这台机床梭子的转速 应该是每分钟三百转
Check the shuttle rotation on this STB. It should be 300 per minute.
这种棉织品 反向线应该是四千根
This kind of cotton weave, the opposing thread count should be 4,000.
嘿 真了不起 是吧?
Hey, this is pretty awesome, huh?
这是幌子吗?
Is it a front?
- 什么的幌子?  - 我不知道
- Front for what?  - I don't know.
杀手组织的
Assassinations.
你也许以为这是幌子
You may think this is a front for something,
我只能告诉你这是一个纺织厂
all I can tell you is this is a textile mill.
乔治... 乔治 去给彼得解释一下
And George... George, go help Peter up there.
好的
Yeah.
这是家纺织厂
This is a textile mill.
而且很不错
And a damn good one.
真棒 不过这是废话吧?
Yeah, that's cute, but that's bullshit, right?
我是说 这些人都是杀手吧 对吗?
I mean, all these guys are killers, aren't they?
我觉得你该回答我几个问题
I think you owe me some answers.
好吧 我显然是不懂
All right. Clearly I don't understand,
你们是做毛衣的还是杀人的?
but do you make sweaters or do you kill people?
喝杯咖啡的时间可回答不了这么多
That's an awful lot of questions over coffee.
你真的准备好听答案了吗?
Are you sure you're ready for the answers?
是的
Yes, I'm sure.
我没法回头了
I can't go back.
回到原来的生活
Not to my life.
他归你了
He's all yours.
好 咱们走
All right. We're up.
你好吗?
How you doing?
我是"维修员"
I'm The Repairman.
你修什么?
What do you repair?
一辈子的坏习惯
A lifetime of bad habits.
- 好吧  - 你帮我个忙好吗?
- Okay. - Would you do me a favour?
把你的手放到身后
Just put your arms behind your back.
- 没事的  - 我不懂...
- It's okay.  - I don't know...
- 放到背后就行  - 这样?
- Just behind your back.  - Is this okay?
放松
Just relax.
这也是训练?
Is this part of it?
我们开始吧
There we go.
- 你要在我头上套个袋子?  - 不 不用袋子
- You going to put a bag over my head?  - No. There's no need for a bag.
- 不会太紧吗?  - 不 这样很好
- That's not too tight, is it?  - No, that's nice.
你为什么来这里 韦斯利?
Why did you come here, Wesley?
是你带我来的 你忘了?
Well, you brought me here, remember?
你他妈的干什么...
What the fuck did you do that...
"维修员"打了他几下...
How many punches did The Repairman throw...
他就晕过去了的?
before he was counting sheep?
以前我不被经常打脸 明白吗?
Well, I haven't spent a lot of time having my face smashed in before, all right?
- 你用刀的次数多吗?  - 早饭 中饭和晚饭时都用
- Did you spend a lot of time with knives? - At breakfast, lunch and dinner.
我靠
Fuck.
刚才那是个反问句 蠢货
It was a rhetorical question, culo.
你要是再插嘴 我就用刀刃了
You interrupt me again, I use the business end.
现在你需要听好了
Here's what you need to know, puto.
刀子很容易隐藏
Knives are easy to hide.
它们不会卡壳 也永远不会用光子弹
They don't jam and they never run out of bullets.
当你要做近距离接触的任务时...
They come in handy...
刀子是非常好用的
when you have to do some close contact work.
老兄 你干吗?
What the fuck, man?
- 过来 过来  - 啥?
- Come here. Come here.  - What?
- 现在 试着砍我  - 什么?
- Now, try to cut me.  - What?
试着砍我 嘿!
Try to cut me. Hey!
- 就用那个捅我...  - 你当心点 这刀很快
- Just stick me with that...  - Be careful with that. That's sharp.
- 你就捅啊捅啊捅  - 为什么?
- Just stick and stick and stick.  - Why?
- 说真的 老兄 我可能会弄伤你  - 喂!
- Seriously, man, I could hurt you.  - Hey!
好吧 胆小鬼
Okay, pussy.
- 我不是胆小鬼  - 你就是胆小鬼
- I'm not a pussy.  - You're a pussy.
- 不 我不是胆小鬼  - 你就是胆小鬼!
- No, I'm not a pussy.  - You're a pussy!
我不是胆小鬼 我只是在意你的健康状况
I'm not a pussy. I got a healthy respect for the human condition.
- 放屁 胆小鬼!  - 我不是胆小鬼!
- Fuck that, you pussy!  - I'm not a pussy!
- 你就是胆小鬼!  - 我不是胆小鬼!
- You're a pussy!  - I'm not a pussy!
- 来吧 胆小鬼  - 我不是胆小鬼!
- Come on, pussy.  - I'm not a pussy!
喂 你怎么样?
Hi. How you doing?
搞什么?
What the fuck?
操!
The fuck!
稍等一下 稍等一下
Just a moment. Just a moment.
对不起
Sorry.
喂? 喂!
Hello? Hey!
回来 喂!
Hey, come back! Hey!
你一定要喝下去 喝下去 对
You must drink. Drink. Yeah.
- 这是哪?  - 这里是康复室
- What is this? - This is the recovery room.
这种药浴可以刺激白血球 加快康复
This bath stimulates white blood cells and speed up the process.
在这里 瘀伤 刀伤 骨折只要几个小时就能好 不用几天
In here, bruises, cuts, breaks heal in hours, not days.
你逗我?
You shitting me?
- 这是什么? 伏特加?  - 对
- What is that? Vodka? - Yeah.
- 你是俄罗斯人?  - 对
- Are you Russian?  - Yeah.
起来
Get up.
这是"枪械师"
This is The Gunsmith.
他对枪械的了解比任何人都多 他会教你怎么用枪
He knows more about a piece than anybody, and he's gonna teach you how to use one.
- 你好吗?  - 很好
- How you doing?  - Pretty good.
- 塞尔泽的腿断了 你知道吗?  - 哦 是吗?
- You know that Seltzer broke his leg?  - Oh, really?
是的 断了三处
Yeah, in three places.
- 怎么弄的?  - 从大楼上跳下来摔的
- How'd he do that?  - Jumped off a building.
- 那他还好吧?  - 还行 不过伤势挺重的
- So, is he okay?  - Yeah. It's pretty bad, though.
天啊
Oh, my God.
天啊 这做得太像真的了
Oh, my God, you guys, that is so realistic.
他已经在康复室呆了三天
He's been in recovery for, like, three days now,
他们说还不能让他出来
and they say they're not even gonna let him out.
天啊
Oh, my God.
天啊!
Oh, my God!
我们不能开枪打死掉的女人! 也许她是什么人的妈妈...
Hey, we can't shoot a dead woman! She might be somebody's mom...
你必须了解子弹打在人身上是什么样的
You need to know what it's like to put a bullet in a body.
你为什么来这儿?
Why are you here?
你知道 我以为我是来学习当超级刺客的
You know, I thought I was learning to be some kind of super assassin.
如果我想挨揍
You know, if I wanted to get beat up,
我就会呆在自己的小办公室隔间里了
I would have stayed in my cubicle, you know.
操
Fuck.
好 射目标
All right, shoot the target.
从哪
From there.
- 你要我射穿死猪?  - 我要你让子弹拐弯
- You want me shoot through Wilbur?  - I want you to curve the bullet.
我怎么才能做到?
How am I suppose to do that?
这不是怎么做的问题
It's not a question of how,
而是做什么
it's a question of what.
如果没有人告诉你子弹是走直线的...
If no one told you that bullets flew straight ...
我给你一把抢 让你去射目标
and I gave you a gun and told you to hit the target,
你会怎么做?
what would you do?
让你的本能引导你
Let your instincts guide you.
他到底怎么做到的?
How the hell did he do that?
你能做到吗? 你能做到吗? 喂?
Can you do that? Can you do that? Hello?
嘿 我觉得那火车我上去过
Hey, I think that's my old train.
你还得上
Still is.
操! 你混蛋!
Shit! You fucking asshole!
来吧!
Come on!
我们走
Let's go.
你是不是疯了?
Are you out of your fucking mind?
天啊 天啊 天啊
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
天啊 我觉得... 我觉得... 我觉得...
Oh, God, I feel... I feel... I feel...
我觉得还不错
I feel kind of good.
他干掉了里克特斯 完美的一枪 不可思议的角度
He got Rictus. Perfect shot. Impossible angle.
克洛斯正在一个一个地杀我们
Cross is taking us out one by one.
韦斯利是唯一能杀掉他的人
And Wesley is the only one who can get to him.
每过一个小时 克洛斯都会离我们进一步
Cross gets closer with each hour.
回去工作
Get back to work.
看见没?
See that?
- 是个梭子  - 对
- It's a shuttle.  - Okay.
我要你想办法抓住它
I want you to try and catch it.
你要我把手伸进去?
You want me to stick my hand in there?
对 我要你抓住它
Yes. I want you to catch it.
你要不要拿枪顶住我的头?
You wanna put a gun to my head?
我眼里的东西就会像苍蝇一样变慢
I can just slow things down like with the flies.
你必须学会自己控制这种能力
You need to learn to control that by yourself.
操 操 操!
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
这真扯淡! 去他妈的!
This is bullshit! Fuck this!
今天怎么样了 韦斯利?
How's it going today, Wesley?
不好 去他妈的织布机 去他妈的维修员!
No. Fuck the loom and fuck The Repairman!
我能打掉苍蝇的翅膀! 我已经准备好了!
I can shoot the wings off the back of a fly! I'm ready!
等到福克斯说你准备好了 你才算是准备好了
You're ready when Fox says you're ready.
- 谁让她负责的?  - 我
- Who put her in charge?  - I did.
韦斯利
Wesley.
别人都以为要抓这些小美人得用奶酪
People think you use cheese to catch these beauties.
其实它们见到花生酱就会发疯
But they go ape-shit for peanut butter.
你父亲特别爱玩这个 看好
Your father was a big fan of this. Watch.
塑性炸药和花生酱!
Plastic explosive and peanut butter!
抱歉 小老鼠
Sorry, Mickey.
五 四 三 二 一
Five, four, three, two, one.
嘿 嘿 俄罗斯人
Hey. Hey, Russian.
这一只很不错
Good for one. Yeah.
要是有一千只会怎样?
Imagine if you had a thousand.
他们也狠狠地整过你 对吗?
They really fucked you up, didn't they?
他们对你做过什么?
What the hell did they do to you?
无缘无故把你扔到高速火车上?
Throw you in front of a moving train for no reason?
把你打得满地找牙?
Beat the shit out of you?
你可以说 这是个鬼地方
You know, you can say it, this place is bullshit. It's bullshit, huh?
操蛋!
Bullshit!
维修员 五分钟后见
Repairman. Five minutes.
你就不能提醒我一下?
Heads up out of the question?
我靠
Fuck.
你他妈的在浪费我的时间! 你为什么来这儿?
You're a waste of my fucking time! Why are you here?
我不知道 揍我吧
I don't know, so hit me.
- 你为什么来这儿?  - 我活得一团糟 为什么不来这儿?
- Why are you here?  - I had a shit life, so why wouldn't I?
我要好好揍你一顿!
I wanna kick your fucking ass!
告诉我你要我说什么
Tell me what you want me to say.
- 你为什么来这儿?  - 我不知道!
- Why are you here?  - I don't know!
你为什么来这?
Why are you here?
- 你为什么来这儿?  - 我不知道!
- Why are you here? - I don't know why I'm here.
你为什么来这?
Why are you here?
我不知道我是谁
I don't know who I am.
- 你说什么?  - 我说...
- What did you say?  - I said...
我不知道我是谁
I said I don't know who I am.
你真的想知道自己是谁?
Do you really want to know who you are?
这是我的房间
Yeah. It's my room.
不
No.
这是你父亲的房间
This was your father's room.
出了什么事?
What happened?
"兄弟会"的一名成员叛变了
A member of this fraternity went rogue.
是克洛斯
Cross.
他一开始就杀了一个比他优秀的人
He started by killing the one man who was better than him.
你父亲
Your father.
在屋顶上偷袭他
Blindsided him on a rooftop.
背叛他
Betrayed him.
这个房间里的一切
Everything in this room,
书 武器 衣服
books, weapons, clothes,
都是他的
belonged to him.
现在归你了
Now they belong to you.
在房间里找找你和他的联系 韦斯利
Find a connection in this room, Wesley.
这可能是唯一知道你是谁的方法
It may be the only way of finding out who you are.
现在我知道了为什么我以前对什么事都不在乎
Now I know why I could never care about anything before this.
我生活在谎言中
I was living a lie.
我终于有机会穿上父亲的鞋子
Finally, I have a chance to step into my father's shoes.
成长起来 过我天生该过的生活
Grow a pair. Live the life I was born to live.
我之前还一直在逃避它 把它当成了又一份该死的结算报告
I've been pissing it all away like it was another fucking billing report.
我要更加努力训练
I have to train harder.
我要想我父亲一样优秀
I have to be as good as my father.
韦斯利 这些架子上放的 是"兄弟会"的刺杀记录
On these shelves, Wesley, are the records of the Fraternity kills,
刺杀目标所需的一切都在这里
everything you will need to kill your target.
要杀克洛斯
To kill Cross,
这个背叛兄弟会 杀害我父亲的家伙 我必须做好准备
the man who betrayed the Fraternity and murdered my father, I must prepare.
我必须成为他的学生 记住他的每一次行动
I have to become his student, memorize every move he ever made,
他的每一次刺杀
every attack he ever executed.
他曾经在被特工处包围的密闭房间里杀掉了一个病人
When he dropped a patient in an airtight room surrounded by Secret Service agents.
他曾经在电梯里干掉了那个商人
When he took out that businessman in the elevator.
当然了 他的子弹是无迹可寻的
His bullets untraceable, of course.
不管他消灭目标时用的是什么武器什么方法
Or how no matter what the weapon or how he eliminated his target,
他总是技高一筹
he was always one chess move ahead.
多留一手
One move more prepared.
多行一步
One step quicker.
多中一枪
One shot more precise.
事实上 我研究了那么多材料 发现他在杀人时从不失手
In fact, in all my research, I found that he never missed a target.
除了杀我那次
Not until me.
是的!
Yeah!
你这辈子第一次能掌控全局了 韦斯利
First time in your life, Wesley, you're in control.
射击目标
Shoot the target.
你疯了
You're crazy.
欢迎加入兄弟会
Welcome to the Fraternity.
我们叫它"命运织布机"
We call this the Loom of Fate.
过了今天 你就再也不能走进这里
After today, you will never set foot in here again.
为什么?
Why not?
因为你就和耶稣的门徒一样
Because, like an apostle,
你的任务不是解密 而是执行
your task is not to interpret, but to deliver.
历史上每一个文明都有一套密码
Every culture in history has a secret code,
那是在传统文字中找不到的
one you won't find in traditional texts.
一千年前
A thousand years ago,
一群织布工发现织物中隐藏着一种神秘的语言
a clan of weavers discovered a mystical language hidden in the fabric.
他们自称"兄弟会"
They called themselves the Fraternity.
跟你说实话 我只看见一根根线
I'll be honest with you, all I see are threads.
过来
Come here.
看那里
Look there.
你有没有看见有一根线没有织进去...
Do you see that one thread that missed the weave...
盖住了其他线?
and lies on top of the others?
- 这是出错了?  - 不 这是密码
- Like a mistake?  - No, it's a code.
如果垂直线在上 那就是一
If the vertical thread is on top, it's a one.
如果在下 那就是零
If it's below, it's a zero.
二进制代码?
Binary code?
这说明什么?
What does it say?
名字
It's a name.
目标
A target.
那些名字是哪来的?
Where do the names come from?
是由必然产生的 韦斯利
Come out of a necessity, Wesley.
为了平衡这个世界的必然
A necessity to maintain balance in the world.
它们是必须被执行的命令
They are orders that must be executed,
我们被赋予在混乱中创造平静的使命
entrusted to us so that we might forge stability out of chaos.
这个是你的
This one is yours.
我不明白...
I don't...
我以为你带我来这里 是让我杀克洛斯
Look, I thought you brought me here to kill Cross.
你会的
You will.
等时间到的时候
In time.
这是你第一个刺杀任务
This is your first assignment.
纺织机提供任务
The loom provides,
我来解密
I interpret,
你去执行
you deliver.
你要我去杀罗伯特・狄恩・达顿?
You want me to kill Robert Deane Darden?
不是我要
Not me.
是命运
Fate.
目标将会在会议室里坐在主席座上
The target will be in the conference room, sitting at the head chair.
一共有六扇窗户
There are six windows.
你从第五扇射击他
You will shoot through the fifth.
第五扇
Fifth window.
动手
Now.
他做错了什么 为什么得死?
What did he do that he deserves to die?
你不知道
You don't know.
我不知道他是否做过坏事 是不是个坏人
I don't know if he was bad, I don't know if he was evil.
我对他一无所知
I don't know anything about him.
我们从个织布机得到命令
We get our orders from a loom.
是命运
Fate.
我们必须坚信自己做得对
And we're supposed to take it on faith that what we're doing is right.
杀掉毫不相识的人
Killing someone we know nothing about,
我觉得我做不到
I don't know if I can do that.
二十年前
About 20 years ago,
有个女孩
there was this girl.
她爸爸是联邦法官
Her dad was a federal judge,
所以她一直觉得自己也会成为一个那样的人
so she probably had it in her mind that she was gonna follow in his footsteps.
有年圣诞节 她一个人在家
So she's home one Christmas,
她爸爸要去处理一起敲诈案
and her dad's on this big racketeering case.
被告想要换一个
The defendants want to get a softer judge.
他们能买通的法官
One they can buy off.
所以他们就雇了一个人
So they hire this guy,
叫马科斯・佩特里奇
Max Petridge,
让他去找她爸爸
get him to pay her father a visit.
这家伙的拜访方式
And the way he pays people a visit
就是闯进他家...
is to break in...
把他的家人绑起来
and tie up their loved ones,
让他们看着...
and force them to watch...
他是如何被活活烧死的
while he burns his targets alive.
然后杀手拿来一个衣架...
And then he takes a wire hanger and twists it round...
把它扭成自己的名字 让别人永远都忘不了他
and brands his initials into each one of them so they will never ever forget.
我加入了兄弟会后
After I was recruited into the Fraternity,
我发现就在联邦法官被杀几星期前...
I found out that Max Petridge's name had come up...
马科斯・佩特里奇就已经是目标了
weeks before the federal judge was killed,
但那个兄弟会成员却不忍心扣下扳机
and that a Fraternity member had failed to pull the trigger.
谁都无法知道自己的决定究竟会有多大影响
We don't know how far the ripples of our decisions go.
杀掉一个人 或许
You kill one, and maybe,
会救了无数无辜的人
save a thousand.
这就是兄弟会的原则
That's the code of the Fraternity.
也是我们的信念和动力
That's what we believe in, and that's why we do it.
动手!
Now!
克洛斯
Cross.
还不行
Not yet.
目标会乘坐一辆黑色豪华轿车
Your target will be in a black limo.
他总是经过霍尔斯特德街的六个街区
He always travels the same six blocks of Halsted.
你可以在其中的三条街杀了他
You have three blocks to kill him.
该死
Shit.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
拜瑞! 能喂喂安娜贝尔吗?
Barry! Could you feed Annabelle?
拜瑞!
Barry!
韦斯利 嘿 你去哪了? 我真的很想你 兄弟
Wesley. Hey, where have you been? I have really missed you, man.
看看谁来了 你个混蛋!
Look at the big man. You fucking asshole! What?
怎么? 你消失了几周
What? You don't show up for weeks,
现在又突然出现 来上厕所?
now you're just gonna stop by and use the bathroom?
你以为你很牛逼?
You think you're a real big shot now, huh?
不 知道吗? 你就是个屁!
No. You know what? You are nothing!
不 你连屁都不如
No, you are less than nothing.
你连拜瑞的一半都赶不上
You're not even half the man that Barry is.
拜瑞 对我好到你都无法想象!
Barry, he pleases me in ways that you've never even heard of!
她是谁 韦斯利? 你的新马子?
Who the hell is she, Wesley? Your new whore?
就是因为她? 她是妓女吧?
Is that what it takes now? You're paying for it?
韦斯利?
Wesley?
他才是真汉子
He's the man.
- 你还好吧?  - 嗯
- You all right?  - Yeah.
- 嗯 我没事  - 坐下 我去找辆车
- Yeah. I'm okay.  - Go sit down. I'm gonna find a car.
总算过去了 我得恢复一下
Big night. I got to get into recovery.
该死
Shit.
混蛋!
Fuck!
牛之眼
Bull's-eye.
他在这里干嘛?
What's he doing here?
- 挺住!  - 坚持住 别闭眼睛
- Come on!  - Come on. Just stay with us.
把他衣服脱下来
Pull back his jacket.
呼吸 快呼吸 好吗?
Breathe. Breathe, all right?
没事了 没事了
It's all right. It's all right. It's all right.
一千
A thousand.
坚持住!
Come on!
- 不要!  - 不! 别闭眼睛
- Come on!  - No! No! Stay with us.
- 别这样  - 睁开眼睛!
- Come on.  - Open your eyes!
别这样!
Come on!
不要这样!
这是他用过的第一颗能追查的子弹
This bullet is the first traceable bullet he's ever used.
是这个人生产的 他叫佩克瓦斯基
It was made by this man. His name is Pekwarsky.
他现在在东摩拉维亚的一个修道院
He works out of what is now a monastery in Eastern Moravia.
这里就是兄弟会的诞生地
This place is where the Fraternity was born.
他在嘲笑我
He's taunting me.
他给我发了一个讯息
He's sending me a message.
我也要回敬他一个
I'm gonna send him one back.
他在引诱你
He's trapping you.
让你去一个他很熟悉的地方
Leading you to a place he knows very well.
我知道 我...
Look, I know this. I...
你们训练我就是为了这个
This is what you trained me for.
你不能独自去
You can't go alone.
只有我一个人去他才会出现 他又不傻
I go alone or he doesn't show. He's not stupid.
听着杀掉兄弟会成员的人是我
Look, a member of the Fraternity is dead because of me.
好吧
Okay.
你去吧
Go.
谢谢
Thank you.
我觉得不应该这样
I don't think that's a good idea.
你的下一个任务
Your next assignment.
佩克瓦斯基吗?
Pekwarsky?
该死
Shit.
你为什么来这里?
What are you doing here?
放下枪
Lower your gun.
你认得这个吧?
You recognise this?
从我肩膀里取出来的
I pulled this out of my shoulder.
用它射击的那个人杀了我爸爸
The guy who put it there killed my father.
我知道是你生产的 告诉我他在哪
Now, I know you made it, so tell me where he is.
子弹是我设计的 但谁用他我可就不负责了
I did mould this, but I can't be responsible for the people who use them.
别废话 告诉我他在哪
I don't give a shit. Tell me where he is.
看看我手指放在哪
Look at my finger.
我可以安排你们见面
I can try and arrange a meet.
你想过改行吗?
Have you ever thought about doing things differently?
什么意思?
How do you mean?
我也说不清
I don't know.
像别人一样
Being somebody else.
做个普通人
Somebody normal.
没想过
No.
该死
Shit.
让开!
Out of the way!
别过来
Stay.
嘿!
Hey!
他在火车上
He's on the train.
只有他
He's alone.
谢谢
Thank you.
不好意思 坐下!
Sorry. I'm sorry. Sit down!
先生 坐下! 我不会伤害你们的
Sir, sit down! Nobody's gonna get hurt.
先生 坐下... 坐下!
Sir, sit... sit down! Sir, sit down!
让开! 坐下! 坐下!
Get out of the way! Sit down! Stay down! Stay down!
坐着别动! 坐下!
Stay down! It's okay! Sit down!
韦斯利
Wesley.
让开! 都让开!
Out of the way! Out of the way!
不 不!
No, no, no!
韦斯利 听我说
Wesley, listen to me.
闭嘴!
Shut the fuck up!
你别跟我说话
You don't get to talk to me.
你不配跟我说话
他们在骗你
Everything they told you was a lie.
闭嘴 你这个混蛋 闭上狗嘴
Shut up, you lying piece of shit. You shut the fuck up.
我是你父亲
You are my son.
你说什么?
What did you say?
你刚才说什么?
What did you say to me?
他说的是真的吗?
Is it true?
是的
Yes.
你们为什么要这么做?
Why did you make me do this?
因为你是唯一让他下不了手的人
Because you are the only person he wouldn't kill.
你早就知道 该死的
You knew, God damn it.
你一直都知道
You knew the entire time.
他的名字出现了
Well, his name came up.
你的也一样
So did yours.
好的 没关系的
No, it was okay. Never mind.
不 不 不是那样的
No. No, it was complete shit.
我答应你爸爸 把你带回这里
I promised your father I'd bring you back here.
搞什么?
What the fuck?
他说只有这样才能让你相信
He said it was the only way you'd believe.
你爸爸总是带着这些照片
Your father was never more than a camera click away.
这是我
That's me.
他是我爸爸
He was my father.
但我杀了他
And I killed him.
对他而言 保护你比他自己的命都重要
To your father, protecting you was worth giving up his life.
保护我?
Protect me?
他想杀了我!
He was trying to fucking kill me!
不 他不是想杀你
No. He wasn't trying to kill you.
他是想救你
He was trying to rescue you.
克洛斯离开兄弟会的时候
When Cross left the Fraternity,
斯隆就一直在找你
Sloan hunted you down.
自从福克斯找上你 他就想把你们分开
Ever since Fox had her teeth in you, he's been trying to separate you from them.
你父亲不希望你加入兄弟会 韦斯利
Your father never wanted you in the Fraternity, Wesley.
他希望你过不一样的生活
He wanted a different path for you,
不要重蹈他的覆辙
with things that he could never have.
能有个家
A home.
- 过着平静的生活  - 不
- Peace.  - No.
他希望你有自己的人生
He hoped you would find your own way.
这个是你父亲留下的
Your father got hold of this.
你来破译吧
Decipher it yourself.
多年前 斯隆就为牟私利 开始捏造目标
Sloan began manufacturing targets of his own for profit years ago.
被你父亲发现了
Your father found out about it.
所以他想做点什么 是吧?
And he was going to do something about it on his own, right?
但斯隆让所有人都与他为敌
But Sloan turned everyone against him.
我父亲的名字没有出现 是吧?
My father's name never even came up, did it?
是的 坚守原则让他成为众矢之的
No. Holding to the code made him a target.
好了
Yes.
- 你让我逃跑?  - 不
- You want me to run?  - No.
我希望你活下去
I want you to live.
你应该过截然不同的人生 韦斯利
You can have a different life, Wesley.
这是你父亲希望的
Like your father wanted for you.
他被我们教得很好
We trained him well.
有一点我父亲说错了
My father was wrong about one thing.
他们说的不都是谎话
Everything they told me wasn't a lie.
他们教会我如何杀人 如何麻木
They taught me how to kill, how to feel no pain,
更重要的是 工欲善其事 必先利其器
and most importantly, that every job has a perfect weapon.
我就是那致命的武器
Well, I'm the perfect weapon.
我应该逃跑?
And I'm supposed to run?
不 我这一辈子都在逃跑
No, I've been doing that my entire life.
所以这次不了
So I say no.
我要杀光他们 其它的就听天由命
I say kill them all and let fate sort out the mess.
杀了他
Kill him.
他在这!
He's here!
胆小鬼
Pussy.
胆小鬼 胆小鬼
Pussy, pussy.
胆小鬼
Pussy.
斯隆!
Sloan!
我父亲不是叛徒
My father wasn't a traitor.
这是杀人指令
This is a kill order.
上面写着斯隆
And it's got Sloan's name on it.
你跟我是怎么说的?
What did you say to me?
这是个名字 一个目标
It's a name. It's a target.
不是我要他死
I don't want this person dead.
但命运如此
Fate does.
命运要你死
Fate wanted you dead.
他无法改变
And he couldn't take it.
所以他为了谋求私利 开始捏造目标
So he started manufacturing his own targets for his own gains.
但我父亲发现了他的阴谋 想要阻止他
And that's when my dad found out and decided to stand against him.
所以你就派我...
And that's when you sent a man's son...
去杀我的父亲
to kill his father.
你不是命运杀手 斯隆
You're not an assassin of fate, Sloan.
你只是一个滥用子弹的暴徒
You're just a thug who can bend bullets.
他说的是真的吗?
Is that true?
真相是这样的
Here is what the truth is.
你的名字出现了
Your name came up.
还有你的名字
Your name.
你的名字
你的
Yours.
这里每个人的名字都出现了
Everyone in this room.
如果我不那么做
If I had not done what I did,
你们早都死了
you would all be dead.
我救了你们
I saved your lives.
看看现在的我们 多么强大
Now look where we are. We are stronger than ever.
改写了历史
Changing the course of history as we see it.
选择了目标
Choosing the targets we select.
我们能够重构权力结构
We can redistribute power where we see fit.
强者生存
The wolves rule.
弱者灭亡
Not the sheep.
如果你们想逐字逐句...
Now, if any of you feel the need to follow the code...
遵守兄弟会的规矩
of the Fraternity to the letter,
那就把枪放进嘴里
I invite you to take your gun,
然后扣动扳机
put it in your mouth and pull the trigger.
韦斯利就想让你们这样
That is what Wesley demands.
或者
Otherwise,
可以杀掉这个混蛋...
shoot this motherfucker...
让杀手兄弟会高一个层次...
and let us take our Fraternity of Assassins to heights...
成为人类的神
reserved only for the gods of men.
你们自己选吧
You choose.
规矩去死吧
Fuck the code.
斯隆!
Sloan!
六周以前 我是个普通人
Six weeks ago, I was ordinary and pathetic.
就像你一样
Just like you.
但现在的我呢?
But who am I now?
是客户经理?
Account manager?
杀手?
Assassin?
还是一个脑残地杀死自己父亲的人?
Or just another tool who was mind-fucked into killing his father?
那都是我
I am all of these.
也都不是我
And I am none of these.
我到底是谁?
Who am I now?
这不是我的命运
This is not me fulfilling my destiny.
也不是追随我父亲的脚步
This is not me following in my father's footsteps.
搜索韦斯利・吉布森 无结果
更不是我拯救了世界
This is definitely not me saving the world.
还在想你是谁?
Still trying to figure out who you are?
那不是我
This is not me.
他只是一个诱饵
This is just a motherfucking decoy.
该死
Oh, fuck.
该我登场了
This is me taking control.
打败斯隆
From Sloan,
打败兄弟会
from the Fraternity,
打败珍妮丝 打败结算报告
from Janice, from billing reports,
打败键盘
from ergonomic keyboards,
打败出轨女友 和不靠谱的朋友
from cheating girlfriends and sack-of-shit best friends.
我要掌控我的...
This is me taking back control...
生活
of my life.
你最近都干了什么?
What the fuck have you done lately?
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影子
翻译: 脸圆圆 一横 初见
校对: 影子